[
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian ethnic group mainly resides in ____ Autonomous Region.",
    "options": [
      "Ningxia",
      "Tibet",
      "Inner Mongolia",
      "Guangxi"
    ],
    "answer": "Inner Mongolia"
  },
  {
    "question": "There are ____ ethnic groups in the Inner Mongolia Autonomous Region.",
    "options": [
      "more than 50",
      "more than 30",
      "more than 20",
      "more than 40"
    ],
    "answer": "more than 50"
  },
  {
    "question": "The entire Inner Mongolia Autonomous Region is mainly composed of ____.",
    "options": [
      "Plateau",
      "Basin",
      "Plain",
      "Hills"
    ],
    "answer": "Plateau"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the western part of Inner Mongolia Autonomous Region, there are Badain Jaran and ____ deserts.",
    "options": [
      "Taklimakan",
      "Tengger",
      "Kubuqi",
      "Qilian Mountains"
    ],
    "answer": "Tengger"
  },
  {
    "question": "Inner Mongolia Autonomous Region has the Great Khingan Mountains, Yin Mountains, and ____ Mountains.",
    "options": [
      "Qinling",
      "Qilian Mountains",
      "Wuyi Mountains",
      "Helan"
    ],
    "answer": "Helan"
  },
  {
    "question": "The natural pastures in Inner Mongolia are mainly distributed in the famous grasslands such as ____ in the country.",
    "options": [
      "Hulunbuir",
      "Ili River Valley",
      "Middle and lower reaches of the Yarlung Zangbo River",
      "Tarim Basin"
    ],
    "answer": "Hulunbuir"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Inner Mongolia Plateau to the west of the Greater Khingan Range in the Inner Mongolia Autonomous Region and to the north of ____ and the Ordos Plateau to the south of the Great Bend of the Yellow River have vegetation cover.",
    "options": [
      "Yinshan Mountains",
      "Tianshan Mountains",
      "Kunlun Mountains",
      "Himalayas"
    ],
    "answer": "Yinshan Mountains"
  },
  {
    "question": "The famous natural pasture in Inner Mongolia does not include ____.",
    "options": [
      "Ulanqab",
      "Kashgar Oasis",
      "Ordos",
      "Urat"
    ],
    "answer": "Kashgar Oasis"
  },
  {
    "question": "The grasslands in Inner Mongolia include ____.",
    "options": [
      "Xilingol",
      "Hetian Oasis",
      "Middle and lower reaches of Yarlung Zangbo River",
      "Southeastern Qinghai"
    ],
    "answer": "Xilingol"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Horqin Grassland in Inner Mongolia is a famous ____ in China.",
    "options": [
      "natural pasture",
      "primeval forest",
      "forestry area",
      "mountain"
    ],
    "answer": "natural pasture"
  },
  {
    "question": "The livestock in Inner Mongolia Autonomous Region mainly consists of ____ and cattle.",
    "options": [
      "yak",
      "sheep",
      "donkey and mule",
      "pig"
    ],
    "answer": "sheep"
  },
  {
    "question": "The livestock in Inner Mongolia Autonomous Region include ____, camels, etc.",
    "options": [
      "horse",
      "highland barley",
      "donkey and mule",
      "wheat"
    ],
    "answer": "horse"
  },
  {
    "question": "The ____ of Inner Mongolia Autonomous Region is a nationally renowned fine livestock breed.",
    "options": [
      "Sanhe Cattle",
      "Hequ Horse",
      "Qinghai Horse",
      "Xinjiang Sheep"
    ],
    "answer": "Sanhe Cattle"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ujumqin fat-tailed sheep is an excellent livestock breed of ____ Autonomous Region.",
    "options": [
      "Inner Mongolia",
      "Qinghai",
      "Tibet",
      "Xinjiang"
    ],
    "answer": "Inner Mongolia"
  },
  {
    "question": "The well-known excellent livestock breeds of the Inner Mongolia Autonomous Region do not include ____. ",
    "options": [
      "Alashan Camel",
      "Black Pig",
      "Albas Cashmere Goat",
      "Sanhe Horse"
    ],
    "answer": "Black Pig"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is one of the fine-wool sheep breeds in the Inner Mongolia Autonomous Region.",
    "options": [
      "Aohan Merino Sheep",
      "Gongbu Mule",
      "Panda",
      "Long-tailed Leaf Monkey"
    ],
    "answer": "Aohan Merino Sheep"
  },
  {
    "question": "Red Steppe cattle is mainly distributed in ____ in China.",
    "options": [
      "Inner Mongolia Autonomous Region",
      "Xinjiang Uygur Autonomous Region",
      "Tibet Autonomous Region",
      "Qinghai Province"
    ],
    "answer": "Inner Mongolia Autonomous Region"
  },
  {
    "question": "To the east of the Greater Khingan Range in Inner Mongolia, there are small parts distributed of the Liao River and the Songnen Plain, known as '____'.",
    "options": [
      "Granary",
      "Jiangnan beyond the Great Wall",
      "Orchard",
      "Medicine storehouse"
    ],
    "answer": "Granary"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Liao River and Songnen Plain area east of the Greater Khingan Mountains in Inner Mongolia is a key area for the country's ____.",
    "options": [
      "agricultural development",
      "animal husbandry development",
      "industrial development",
      "technology development"
    ],
    "answer": "agricultural development"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Yinshan Mountains are composed of ____, Wula Mountains, and Lang Mountains.",
    "options": [
      "Daqing Mountain",
      "Gangdise Mountain",
      "Qilian Mountain",
      "Tanggula Mountain"
    ],
    "answer": "Daqing Mountain"
  },
  {
    "question": "The two plains extremely beneficial for agricultural production in the Inner Mongolia region are the Hetao Plain and the ____ Plain.",
    "options": [
      "Tumochuan",
      "Qinghai",
      "Kunlun",
      "Kazakh"
    ],
    "answer": "Tumochuan"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Yinshan Mountain Range has formed a natural barrier, which is beneficial to the ____ plain south of the Yinshan Mountains in the Inner Mongolia region.",
    "options": [
      "Hetao",
      "Loess",
      "Tibet",
      "Hengduan"
    ],
    "answer": "Hetao"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Hetao Plain in the southern foothills of the Yin Mountains and the ____ Plain are important agricultural production areas in the Inner Mongolia region.",
    "options": [
      "Tumochuan",
      "Kunlun",
      "Himalaya",
      "Qinghai"
    ],
    "answer": "Tumochuan"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Hetao Plain and Tumochuan Plain on the southern slope of Yinshan are known for their fertile soil, intersecting ditches, and abundant farmland, famously referred to as '____'.",
    "options": [
      "Granary of the North",
      "Desert Oasis",
      "Jiangnan Beyond the Great Wall",
      "Pearl of the Gobi"
    ],
    "answer": "Granary of the North"
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the main grain-producing areas in Inner Mongolia is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Northern slope of Tianshan",
      "Kashgar Oasis",
      "Hetao Plain",
      "Ili River Valley"
    ],
    "answer": "Hetao Plain"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main grain-producing areas in Inner Mongolia are located in ____ and the Tumochuan Plain.",
    "options": [
      "Yarlung Zangbo River Basin",
      "South of the Tianshan Mountains",
      "Hetao Plain",
      "Hotan Oasis"
    ],
    "answer": "Hetao Plain"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Tumochuan Plain is the main ____ of Inner Mongolia.",
    "options": [
      "forestry area",
      "rapeseed production area",
      "grain production area",
      "fruit production area"
    ],
    "answer": "grain production area"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main crops in Inner Mongolia include ____.",
    "options": [
      "corn",
      "peas",
      "glutinous rice",
      "rice"
    ],
    "answer": "corn"
  },
  {
    "question": "Among the crops in Inner Mongolia, ____ is an oil crop.",
    "options": [
      "Flax",
      "Peas",
      "Highland Barley",
      "Potatoes"
    ],
    "answer": "Flax"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Hetao Plain in Inner Mongolia is one of China's three major ____ production areas.",
    "options": [
      "rapeseed",
      "sugar beet",
      "potato",
      "rice"
    ],
    "answer": "sugar beet"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Yellow River flows through the ____ part of the region inhabited by the Mongolian ethnic group.",
    "options": [
      "South",
      "East",
      "West",
      "Southwest"
    ],
    "answer": "Southwest"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian inhabited areas are famous for producing ____.",
    "options": [
      "Yellow River carp",
      "Ili fruit",
      "saffron",
      "Tianshan wool"
    ],
    "answer": "Yellow River carp"
  },
  {
    "question": "Among the larger lakes in Inner Mongolia, which lake is known as 'the lake where the noise of fish is loud and horses refuse to drink'?",
    "options": [
      "Hulun Lake",
      "Qinghai Lake",
      "Ili River",
      "Ulan Suhai"
    ],
    "answer": "Hulun Lake"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lakes in Inner Mongolia that produce a large number of carp include Hulun Lake, Buir Lake, Ulan Suhai, Daihai, and ____.",
    "options": [
      "Huangqihai Lake",
      "Qinghai Lake",
      "Xinjiang Lake",
      "Ili Lake"
    ],
    "answer": "Huangqihai Lake"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hulun Lake, Buir Lake, Ulan Suhai, and Daihai all belong to the lakes of the ____ nationality region.",
    "options": [
      "Mongolian",
      "Kazakh",
      "Tibetan",
      "Uyghur"
    ],
    "answer": "Mongolian"
  },
  {
    "question": "The fish species that is not commonly found in the lakes of Inner Mongolia is ______.",
    "options": [
      "Silverfish",
      "Silver carp",
      "Carp",
      "Salmon"
    ],
    "answer": "Salmon"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Inner Mongolia region, there are hundreds of ____ such as Dabusu and Jilantai.",
    "options": [
      "Iron rope bridge",
      "Vine net bridge",
      "Salt pond",
      "Rapeseed field"
    ],
    "answer": "Salt pond"
  },
  {
    "question": "There are hundreds of salt ponds and alkaline lakes in Inner Mongolia, which are rich in ____.",
    "options": [
      "Yuangen",
      "Radish",
      "Mirabilite",
      "Salt and Alkali"
    ],
    "answer": "Salt and Alkali"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Jilantai Salt Field is the largest ____ in the Inner Mongolia region and also in China.",
    "options": [
      "mountainous area",
      "mechanized lake salt field",
      "warm river valley area",
      "Jiangnan beyond the Great Wall"
    ],
    "answer": "mechanized lake salt field"
  },
  {
    "question": "Jilantai Salt Field is the largest mechanized lake salt field in China, and it is also the largest ____ processing base.",
    "options": [
      "iodized salt",
      "potato",
      "rapeseed",
      "apple"
    ],
    "answer": "iodized salt"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Jilantai Salt Field is not only the largest mechanized lake salt field in China, but also a lake salt area and a ____ processing base.",
    "options": [
      "walnut",
      "iodized salt",
      "rattan net bridge",
      "simple wooden bridge"
    ],
    "answer": "iodized salt"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Greater Khingan Range is known as the '____ treasure trove of the motherland'.",
    "options": [
      "Golden",
      "Green",
      "Red",
      "Blue"
    ],
    "answer": "Green"
  },
  {
    "question": "The types of Mongolian herbal medicine include ____.",
    "options": [
      "Snow lotus",
      "Licorice",
      "Ganoderma",
      "Polygonum multiflorum"
    ],
    "answer": "Licorice"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Inner Mongolia grassland has been the stage where ancient _____ ethnic minorities of our country were active and galloped.",
    "options": [
      "Northern",
      "Southern",
      "Western",
      "Eastern"
    ],
    "answer": "Northern"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian ethnic group is mainly distributed on the ____ grassland.",
    "options": [
      "Xinjiang",
      "Yulong",
      "Qinghai",
      "Inner Mongolia"
    ],
    "answer": "Inner Mongolia"
  },
  {
    "question": "The ethnic group that did not leave a rich cultural heritage on the Inner Mongolia grassland is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Xiongnu",
      "Uyghur",
      "Wuhuan",
      "Chile"
    ],
    "answer": "Uyghur"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hohhot's ____ is an important cultural heritage of the Inner Mongolia grassland.",
    "options": [
      "Tibet Temple",
      "Wudang Zhao",
      "Five Pagoda Temple",
      "Qinghai Tower"
    ],
    "answer": "Five Pagoda Temple"
  },
  {
    "question": "The ____ in Baotou City, Inner Mongolia, is one of the important cultural heritages.",
    "options": [
      "Daming Tower",
      "Genghis Khan Mausoleum",
      "Meidaizhao Monastery",
      "Potala Palace"
    ],
    "answer": "Meidaizhao Monastery"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ in Ejin Horo Banner is a famous cultural heritage of the Inner Mongolia grassland.",
    "options": [
      "Gaxian Cave",
      "Five Pagoda Temple",
      "Tomb of Wang Zhaojun",
      "Mausoleum of Genghis Khan"
    ],
    "answer": "Mausoleum of Genghis Khan"
  },
  {
    "question": "The ____ and Dazhao Temple in Hohhot are both important cultural heritages.",
    "options": [
      "Five Pagoda Temple",
      "Mosque",
      "Sakya Monastery",
      "Potala Palace"
    ],
    "answer": "Five Pagoda Temple"
  },
  {
    "question": "Chifeng's ____ is one of the important cultural heritages of the Inner Mongolia grasslands.",
    "options": [
      "Liao Dynasty's Shangjing",
      "Lama Temple",
      "Kumbum Monastery",
      "Qinghai Tower"
    ],
    "answer": "Liao Dynasty's Shangjing"
  },
  {
    "question": "The capital of Inner Mongolia Autonomous Region, Hohhot, means the city of ____.",
    "options": [
      "Green",
      "White",
      "Black",
      "Red"
    ],
    "answer": "Green"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hohhot was built in ____.",
    "options": [
      "Qing Dynasty",
      "Yuan Dynasty",
      "Tang Dynasty",
      "Ming Dynasty"
    ],
    "answer": "Ming Dynasty"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hohhot was originally called ____ when it was built.",
    "options": [
      "Kukuhetun",
      "Dali Ancient City",
      "Changde Fu City",
      "Shunde City"
    ],
    "answer": "Kukuhetun"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the 16th year of the Ming Wanli era (1588), Hohhot was officially named as ____.",
    "options": [
      "Almaty",
      "Lhasa",
      "Guihua",
      "Korla"
    ],
    "answer": "Guihua"
  },
  {
    "question": "\"Kukuhetun\" is an alternative translation of ____.",
    "options": [
      "Hohhot",
      "Urumqi",
      "Lhasa",
      "Kunming"
    ],
    "answer": "Hohhot"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian language belongs to the ____ language family of the Altaic language group.",
    "options": [
      "Mongolian",
      "Tibetan",
      "Uyghur",
      "Kazakh"
    ],
    "answer": "Mongolian"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian language of China's Mongolian ethnic group can be divided into Inner Mongolia, Oirat, and ____ dialects.",
    "options": [
      "Barga Buryat",
      "Kharchin",
      "Hotan",
      "Lop"
    ],
    "answer": "Barga Buryat"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the early 13th century, the Mongolian people created their own script based on ____.",
    "options": [
      "Uighur script",
      "Arabic script",
      "Turkic runes",
      "Sogdian script"
    ],
    "answer": "Uighur script"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Yuan Dynasty Emperor Kublai Khan ordered the Tibetan Lama Phagpa to create a new Mongolian script, commonly known as '____'.",
    "options": [
      "Phags-pa script",
      "Latin alphabet new script",
      "Dynastic Turkic script",
      "Saka script"
    ],
    "answer": "Phags-pa script"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yuan Emperor Kublai Khan ordered ____ to create a new Mongolian script, commonly known as 'Phagspa script'.",
    "options": [
      "Tibetan Lama Phagspa",
      "Ancestors of the Kazakh ethnicity",
      "Uyghurs from the Onion Ridge west",
      "Ancient Saka people from the Seven Rivers region"
    ],
    "answer": "Tibetan Lama Phagspa"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Phagspa script was created based on modifications to ____.",
    "options": [
      "Tibetan script",
      "Uyghur script",
      "Latin alphabet",
      "Arabic alphabet"
    ],
    "answer": "Tibetan script"
  },
  {
    "question": "\"The 'Phags-pa script' was ____ during the Yuan Dynasty.",
    "options": [
      "Dynasty Turkic script",
      "National script",
      "Chagatai script",
      "Tibetan script"
    ],
    "answer": "National script"
  },
  {
    "question": "The 'Phags-pa script was basically no longer used after ____.",
    "options": [
      "Creation of Tibetan script",
      "Establishment of the Kara-Khanid Khanate by the Kõn-lung West Uighurs and Karluks, adopting Islam",
      "Collapse of the Yuan Dynasty",
      "Establishment of the Chagatai Khanate"
    ],
    "answer": "Collapse of the Yuan Dynasty"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the early 14th century, the Mongolian scholar ____ reformed the initial Mongolian script.",
    "options": [
      "Chos-kyi Hod-zer",
      "Oghuz Khan",
      "Genghis Khan",
      "Temüjin"
    ],
    "answer": "Chos-kyi Hod-zer"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the early 14th century, the Mongolian scholar Chos-kyi Hod-zer reformed the Mongolian script, which became the Mongolian script that is ____ to this day.",
    "options": [
      "commonly used",
      "ancient",
      "difficult to understand",
      "disappeared"
    ],
    "answer": "commonly used"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian ethnic group in Xinjiang uses ____.",
    "options": [
      "Uyghur Central Dialect",
      "Oirat Dialect",
      "Tibetan Kham Dialect",
      "Chinese"
    ],
    "answer": "Oirat Dialect"
  },
  {
    "question": "The inventor of Todo bichig is _____.",
    "options": [
      "Zaya Pandita",
      "Karakhan Khan",
      "Oghuz Khan",
      "Wangchao Turkic"
    ],
    "answer": "Zaya Pandita"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the mid-17th century, Zaya Pandita made slight changes to the universal Mongolian script, which is known as _____.",
    "options": [
      "Todo Bichig",
      "Dynastic Turkic script",
      "Uyghur script",
      "Kazakh script"
    ],
    "answer": "Todo Bichig"
  },
  {
    "question": "Todo Bichig means _____.",
    "options": [
      "clear script",
      "basic script",
      "popular script",
      "ancient script"
    ],
    "answer": "precise script"
  },
  {
    "question": "Todo Bichig is used to accurately convey the _____ phonetics.",
    "options": [
      "Oirat",
      "Turkic",
      "Kazakh",
      "Uyghur"
    ],
    "answer": "Oirat"
  },
  {
    "question": "The script known as 'Todo' (Tote) Mongolian was invented in the _____ century.",
    "options": [
      "17",
      "15",
      "10",
      "9"
    ],
    "answer": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian ethnic group is an ancient ____ nationality in northern China.",
    "options": [
      "nomadic",
      "fishing and hunting",
      "farming",
      "fishing village"
    ],
    "answer": "nomadic"
  },
  {
    "question": "In ancient times, the Mongolian ethnic group was mainly engaged in ____ industry.",
    "options": [
      "Animal husbandry",
      "Fishing",
      "Mining",
      "Farming"
    ],
    "answer": "Animal husbandry"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian ethnic group established and developed ____ in modern society.",
    "options": [
      "Processing industry and industry",
      "Agriculture and fishery",
      "Animal husbandry and fishery",
      "Fishery and hunting"
    ],
    "answer": "Processing industry and industry"
  },
  {
    "question": "In modern society, the processing industry and ____ of the Mongolian ethnic group have developed.",
    "options": [
      "industry",
      "agriculture",
      "animal husbandry",
      "fishery"
    ],
    "answer": "industry"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main economic production method that the Mongolian people historically relied on for survival and development is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Agriculture",
      "Fishing",
      "Animal husbandry",
      "Craft making"
    ],
    "answer": "Animal husbandry"
  },
  {
    "question": "The primary source of sustenance and clothing for the Mongolian ethnic group comes from ____.",
    "options": [
      "Livestock products",
      "Agricultural products",
      "Handicrafts",
      "Fishery products"
    ],
    "answer": "Livestock products"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main historical stage of the Mongolian ethnic group is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Xinjiang Grassland",
      "Inner Mongolia Grassland",
      "Qinghai-Tibet Plateau",
      "Northeast Plain"
    ],
    "answer": "Inner Mongolia Grassland"
  },
  {
    "question": "The clothing of the Mongolian ethnic group is determined by the ____ living environment.",
    "options": [
      "Mongolian grasslands",
      "Qinghai-Tibet Plateau",
      "Desert",
      "Mountainous area"
    ],
    "answer": "Mongolian grasslands"
  },
  {
    "question": "The traditional clothing of the Mongolian people is ____.",
    "options": [
      "robe",
      "qipao",
      "Zhongshan suit",
      "changshan"
    ],
    "answer": "robe"
  },
  {
    "question": "The characteristic of traditional Mongolian costumes is ____.",
    "options": [
      "loose",
      "tight-fitting",
      "short",
      "slit"
    ],
    "answer": "loose"
  },
  {
    "question": "The winter clothing in the Mongolian pastoral areas is mostly____.",
    "options": [
      "leather clothing",
      "down jacket",
      "sweater",
      "military coat"
    ],
    "answer": "leather clothing"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian ethnic group generally wears ____ type of clothing in the summer.",
    "options": [
      "fur",
      "silk",
      "cloth",
      "linen"
    ],
    "answer": "cloth"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian ethnic group's clothing usually prefers ____ color.",
    "options": [
      "Blue",
      "Black",
      "White",
      "Pink"
    ],
    "answer": "Blue"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mongolian people like to use ____ as a belt.",
    "options": [
      "red and green silk",
      "blue fabric",
      "yellow silk",
      "cotton cloth"
    ],
    "answer": "red and green silk"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mongolian people hang ____ on their waists, which can be used to eat meat.",
    "options": [
      "knife",
      "fork",
      "spoon",
      "chopsticks"
    ],
    "answer": "knife"
  },
  {
    "question": "Among the items that the Mongolian people carry with them, it includes ____.",
    "options": [
      "Fire Mother",
      "Fire striker",
      "Flame",
      "Lamp"
    ],
    "answer": "Fire striker"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mongolian people often carry which item with them?",
    "options": [
      "Jade pendant",
      "Smoking pipe",
      "Snuff bottle",
      "Lantern"
    ],
    "answer": "Snuff bottle"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mongolian people like to wear ____, which extend to the knees.",
    "options": [
      "soft-topped leather boots",
      "embroidered cloth shoes",
      "wide-footed straw sandals",
      "pointed wooden clogs"
    ],
    "answer": "soft-topped leather boots"
  },
  {
    "question": "The clothing characteristics of the Mongolian people are adapted to ____.",
    "options": [
      "the natural environment of the prairie pastoral area",
      "urban modernization",
      "the agricultural production method",
      "the plateau mountainous environment"
    ],
    "answer": "the natural environment of the prairie pastoral area"
  },
  {
    "question": "The lifestyle of the Mongolian people is ____, which is one of the reasons for their clothing characteristics.",
    "options": [
      "nomadic life spent moving outside",
      "settled agricultural life",
      "life of sea fishing",
      "urban industrial and commercial life"
    ],
    "answer": "nomadic life spent moving outside"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the farming areas of the Mongolian ethnic group, in winter farmers mostly wear ____.",
    "options": [
      "cloth clothes",
      "felt boots",
      "homespun pants",
      "Urga robe"
    ],
    "answer": "felt boots"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the clothing of Mongolian farmers, ____ is worn less frequently.",
    "options": [
      "cloth garment",
      "shirt",
      "high boots",
      "cotton-padded jacket"
    ],
    "answer": "high boots"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the farming areas of the Mongolian ethnic group, farmers usually tie ____.",
    "options": [
      "cloth belt",
      "silk ribbon",
      "rattan",
      "leather belt"
    ],
    "answer": "cloth belt"
  },
  {
    "question": "The types of clothing among Mongolian farmers include ____.",
    "options": [
      "Cotton-padded jacket",
      "Smooth leather boots",
      "Woolen pants",
      "Leather pants"
    ],
    "answer": "Cotton-padded jacket"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mongolian men like to wear ____ colored hats.",
    "options": [
      "red",
      "blue",
      "white",
      "green"
    ],
    "answer": "blue"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mongolian men also use ____ to wrap around their heads.",
    "options": [
      "silk scarf",
      "satin",
      "towel",
      "belt"
    ],
    "answer": "satin"
  },
  {
    "question": "In addition to blue hats, Mongolian men also like to wear hats of which color?",
    "options": [
      "Red",
      "Black",
      "White",
      "Yellow"
    ],
    "answer": "Black"
  },
  {
    "question": "In addition to blue and black hats, Mongolian men also like to wear hats of which color?",
    "options": [
      "Pink",
      "Yellow",
      "Brown",
      "Green"
    ],
    "answer": "Brown"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mongolian women usually wrap their ____ with red and blue cloth.",
    "options": [
      "head",
      "waist",
      "arms",
      "legs"
    ],
    "answer": "head"
  },
  {
    "question": "In winter, Mongolian women, like men, wear a hat in the shape of ____.",
    "options": [
      "cone",
      "round",
      "flat top",
      "pointed top"
    ],
    "answer": "cone"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unmarried Mongolian women part their hair from ____ and tie it into two braids.",
    "options": [
      "the middle",
      "the top",
      "the left",
      "the right"
    ],
    "answer": "the middle"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unmarried Mongolian women's hair roots carry ____.",
    "options": [
      "two big round beads",
      "a flower rope",
      "a gold ring",
      "two colored ribbons"
    ],
    "answer": "two big round beads"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unmarried women of the Mongolian ethnic group often use ____ to adorn their hair.",
    "options": [
      "Agate, coral, jade",
      "Silver ornaments, copper ornaments, floral cloth",
      "Feathers, colorful stones, shells",
      "Jadeite, amber, crystal stones"
    ],
    "answer": "Agate, coral, jade"
  },
  {
    "question": "The ends of Mongolian girls' hair are usually ____.",
    "options": [
      "drooping",
      "upturned",
      "straight",
      "knotted"
    ],
    "answer": "drooping"
  },
  {
    "question": "Modern Mongolian men wear ____.",
    "options": [
      "suit and tie",
      "long belt around the waist",
      "single braid hairstyle",
      "traditional ethnic clothing"
    ],
    "answer": "suit and tie"
  },
  {
    "question": "Traditional Mongolian clothing is usually worn during ____ activities.",
    "options": [
      "celebrating the harvest",
      "Ovoo worship",
      "family gatherings",
      "neighborhood visits"
    ],
    "answer": "Ovoo worship"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Naadam Festival of the Mongolian ethnic group is an occasion for ____.",
    "options": [
      "Ancestor Worship",
      "Purchasing New Year Goods",
      "Sports Competition",
      "Cultural Exchange"
    ],
    "answer": "Cultural Exchange"
  },
  {
    "question": "The diet in the Mongolian pastoral areas mainly consists of ____.",
    "options": [
      "beef, mutton and dairy products",
      "tsampa",
      "rice and noodles",
      "fried green barley"
    ],
    "answer": "beef, mutton and dairy products"
  },
  {
    "question": "The diet in the Mongolian pastoral area is mainly based on beef, mutton, and dairy products, supplemented by ____.",
    "options": [
      "vegetables and fruits",
      "rice and noodles",
      "grains and vegetables",
      "fried qingke barley"
    ],
    "answer": "grains and vegetables"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mongolian people eat ____ and drink milk tea in the morning.",
    "options": [
      "fried rice",
      "qingtuan",
      "rice sausage",
      "soup noodles"
    ],
    "answer": "fried rice"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the milk tea of the Mongolian ethnic group, butter and a small amount of ____ are added.",
    "options": [
      "chili powder",
      "green salt",
      "barley flour",
      "pepper powder"
    ],
    "answer": "green salt"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mongolians like to eat ____ for lunch and dinner.",
    "options": [
      "Beef and mutton",
      "Pilaf",
      "Noodles",
      "Fish"
    ],
    "answer": "Beef and mutton"
  },
  {
    "question": "An essential necessity for Mongolian herders is ____.",
    "options": [
      "brick tea",
      "horse intestine",
      "beef sausage",
      "stir-fried slices of meat"
    ],
    "answer": "brick tea"
  },
  {
    "question": "When brewing brick tea, the Mongolian ethnic group will add a little ____.",
    "options": [
      "fresh milk",
      "cheese",
      "lemon",
      "fruit"
    ],
    "answer": "fresh milk"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main fuel for Mongolian herders to cook meals and boil tea is ____.",
    "options": [
      "cow dung",
      "musk",
      "antler",
      "firewood"
    ],
    "answer": "cow dung"
  },
  {
    "question": "The diet in rural areas of the Mongolian ethnic group primarily consists of ____.",
    "options": [
      "dairy products",
      "beef and mutton",
      "grains",
      "pilaf"
    ],
    "answer": "grains"
  },
  {
    "question": "The traditional dwelling tool of Mongolian herders is ____.",
    "options": [
      "yurt",
      "felt house",
      "board house",
      "grass house"
    ],
    "answer": "yurt"
  },
  {
    "question": "The shape of a yurt is ____.",
    "options": [
      "circular",
      "square",
      "rectangular",
      "triangular"
    ],
    "answer": "circular"
  },
  {
    "question": "The design of the yurt is suitable for ____ life.",
    "options": [
      "nomadic",
      "settled",
      "fishing and hunting",
      "agricultural"
    ],
    "answer": "nomadic"
  },
  {
    "question": "The general height of a yurt is____.",
    "options": [
      "five to six feet",
      "seven to eight feet",
      "two and a half meters",
      "one zhang"
    ],
    "answer": "seven to eight feet"
  },
  {
    "question": "The wall of a yurt is called ____.",
    "options": [
      "Woni",
      "Umbrella-shaped roof frame",
      "Hana",
      "Radiating poles"
    ],
    "answer": "Hana"
  },
  {
    "question": "The umbrella-shaped top frame of a yurt is called ____.",
    "options": [
      "Hana",
      "Woni",
      "Rafters",
      "Leizi"
    ],
    "answer": "Woni"
  },
  {
    "question": "The top of a yurt is covered with ____.",
    "options": [
      "thick felt",
      "reed mat",
      "branches",
      "mud"
    ],
    "answer": "thick felt"
  },
  {
    "question": "The yurt is surrounded by ____.",
    "options": [
      "hair rope",
      "upright posts",
      "bamboo strips",
      "rattan"
    ],
    "answer": "hair rope"
  },
  {
    "question": "The central top of a yurt has a ____ for ventilation and sunlight absorption.",
    "options": [
      "window",
      "skylight",
      "chimney",
      "vent"
    ],
    "answer": "skylight"
  },
  {
    "question": "The central skylight at the top of the yurt is used for ____ and absorbing sunlight.",
    "options": [
      "dehumidification",
      "heating",
      "ventilation",
      "aesthetic"
    ],
    "answer": "ventilation"
  },
  {
    "question": "In some pastoral and semi-agricultural pastoral areas, ____ structure yurts are used.",
    "options": [
      "bamboo and wood",
      "brick and tile",
      "earth and wood",
      "reinforced steel"
    ],
    "answer": "earth and wood"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Yeke-juu League area, some Mongolian yurts with wooden structures are called ____.",
    "options": [
      "Dugui",
      "Zhanfang",
      "Cangfang",
      "Gandalei"
    ],
    "answer": "Dugui"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Mongolian culture, a type of architecture known as 'Dugui' is a ____.",
    "options": [
      "round",
      "polygonal",
      "square",
      "pentagonal"
    ],
    "answer": "round"
  },
  {
    "question": "The kang (a heated bed platform) commonly built in the houses of the Mongolian ethnic group is usually ____.",
    "options": [
      "north-south or east",
      "east or west",
      "south or west",
      "north or west"
    ],
    "answer": "north-south or east"
  },
  {
    "question": "The structure of Mongolian housing is similar to ____ housing.",
    "options": [
      "Tibetan style",
      "Han style",
      "Uyghur style",
      "Miao style"
    ],
    "answer": "Han style"
  },
  {
    "question": "As the nomadic customs of the Mongolian ethnic group shift towards fixed-point grazing or semi-stabling, the Mongolian people have almost completely settled in ____.",
    "options": [
      "Yurts",
      "Cabins",
      "Brick houses or buildings",
      "Thatched cottages"
    ],
    "answer": "Brick houses or buildings"
  },
  {
    "question": "The customs of the Mongolian ethnic group have gradually shifted from nomadism to ____.",
    "options": [
      "fixed-point grazing or semi-shelter feeding",
      "complete farming",
      "living by hunting",
      "mainly fishing"
    ],
    "answer": "fixed-point grazing or semi-shelter feeding"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the past, the means and methods of transportation in Mongolian production and life were mainly ____.",
    "options": [
      "riding horses",
      "riding ox carts",
      "walking",
      "driving cars"
    ],
    "answer": "riding horses"
  },
  {
    "question": "Apart from horse riding, the traditional means of transportation of the Mongolian ethnic group also includes ____.",
    "options": [
      "Leleche (traditional cart)",
      "Bicycle",
      "Ox cart",
      "Motorcycle"
    ],
    "answer": "Leleche (traditional cart)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Many Mongolian herders own multiple ____ for production and living.",
    "options": [
      "bicycles",
      "boats",
      "livestock",
      "motor vehicles"
    ],
    "answer": "motor vehicles"
  },
  {
    "question": "When herding, Mongolian herders not only ride motorcycles but also drive ____.",
    "options": [
      "motorcycles",
      "jeeps",
      "tractors",
      "aircraft"
    ],
    "answer": "jeeps"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian ethnic group is a very ____ , hospitable, and straightforward ethnicity.",
    "options": [
      "introverted",
      "enthusiastic",
      "conservative",
      "silent"
    ],
    "answer": "enthusiastic"
  },
  {
    "question": "On the vast grassland, there are no ____, but the owner of the yurt will entertain guests.",
    "options": [
      "stores",
      "streetlights",
      "inns",
      "hospitals"
    ],
    "answer": "inns"
  },
  {
    "question": "In every yurt, the host will entertain unfamiliar guests ____.",
    "options": [
      "reluctantly",
      "cheerfully",
      "helplessly",
      "hesitantly"
    ],
    "answer": "cheerfully"
  },
  {
    "question": "When hosting guests, Mongolians will serve ____.",
    "options": [
      "yogurt",
      "milk tea",
      "soy milk",
      "coffee"
    ],
    "answer": "milk tea"
  },
  {
    "question": "When entertaining guests, the Mongolian people will serve ____.",
    "options": [
      "red wine",
      "beer",
      "milk wine",
      "yellow wine"
    ],
    "answer": "milk wine"
  },
  {
    "question": "When entertaining guests, Mongolians will cook ____.",
    "options": [
      "pork",
      "chicken",
      "beef",
      "mutton"
    ],
    "answer": "mutton"
  },
  {
    "question": "When hosting guests, Mongolians may use ____ to urge them to drink.",
    "options": [
      "poetry",
      "dance",
      "song",
      "painting"
    ],
    "answer": "song"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Mongolian culture, when warmly welcoming guests, it might involve ____.",
    "options": [
      "present flowers",
      "offer a khata",
      "give a cheek kiss",
      "present raisins"
    ],
    "answer": "offer a khata"
  },
  {
    "question": "When saying goodbye to guests, the Mongolian people often accompany them for a long distance, ____, showing great warmth.",
    "options": [
      "give directions",
      "help them dismount",
      "see them off beyond the gate",
      "sit at the top center of the house"
    ],
    "answer": "give directions"
  },
  {
    "question": "After the founding of the People's Republic of China, the marriage system implemented by the Mongolian ethnic group was ____.",
    "options": [
      "Monogamy",
      "Polygyny",
      "Polyandry",
      "Free love and marriage system"
    ],
    "answer": "Monogamy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mongolian young men and women become mainstream through ____.",
    "options": [
      "Arranged marriages by parents",
      "Free love and independent mate choice",
      "Matchmaker introduction",
      "Collective wedding"
    ],
    "answer": "Free love and independent mate choice"
  },
  {
    "question": "Due to the lack of labor force, some Mongolian families will____.",
    "options": [
      "bring a son-in-law into the family",
      "divide family property and establish another household",
      "migrate together",
      "exchange marriages without dowry"
    ],
    "answer": "bring a son-in-law into the family"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Alxa League in the west, the Mongolian term for inviting a son-in-law is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Wang Chao Turkic script",
      "Karakhanid Khanate",
      "Khürgen avna",
      "Awule"
    ],
    "answer": "Khürgen avna"
  },
  {
    "question": "After being hired as a son-in-law by the Mongolian ethnic group, he is considered ____.",
    "options": [
      "a follower of Islam",
      "living in a dome warehouse",
      "a family member",
      "a blood relative"
    ],
    "answer": "a family member"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which region does the Mongolian ethnic group, after a son-in-law has been invited and after a certain period, the father-in-law may allocate a portion of property for them to live separately?",
    "options": [
      "Alxa League",
      "Xinjiang",
      "Sichuan",
      "Guangxi"
    ],
    "answer": "Alxa League"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Mongolian custom of separation, if the father-in-law thinks it is time to live apart, he will __.",
    "options": [
      "allocate a portion of property to the son-in-law",
      "not allocate land to the son-in-law",
      "not allocate livestock to the son-in-law",
      "not allocate cash to the son-in-law"
    ],
    "answer": "allocate a portion of property to the son-in-law"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Eastern Mongolian people refer to recruiting a son-in-law as '____', which means a hired son-in-law.",
    "options": [
      "Nika",
      "Khuchin khürgen",
      "Buršak",
      "Dui Qin"
    ],
    "answer": "Khuchin khürgen"
  },
  {
    "question": "The 'Khuchin khürgen' of the Eastern Mongolian ethnic group is manifested as a ____ relationship.",
    "options": [
      "Marriage",
      "Employment",
      "Kinship",
      "Affinity"
    ],
    "answer": "Employment"
  },
  {
    "question": "The 'Khuchin khürgen' of the Eastern Mongols is not recognized as ____.",
    "options": [
      "family members",
      "relatives",
      "employment",
      "bride price"
    ],
    "answer": "family members"
  },
  {
    "question": "In modern society, in Mongolian families where the groom has many brothers and the bride's family has no boys, they might choose the lifestyle of ____.",
    "options": [
      "uxorilocal residence",
      "exchange marriage",
      "bride price",
      "betrothal"
    ],
    "answer": "uxorilocal residence"
  },
  {
    "question": "Before the founding of the People's Republic of China, the funeral methods of the Mongolian people included cremation, burial, and ____.",
    "options": [
      "scattering burial",
      "pagoda burial",
      "exposure burial",
      "water burial"
    ],
    "answer": "exposure burial"
  },
  {
    "question": "In traditional Mongolian culture, the burial practices do not include ____. ",
    "options": [
      "cremation",
      "earth burial",
      "tower burial",
      "sky burial"
    ],
    "answer": "tower burial"
  },
  {
    "question": "Before the founding of the new China, ____ was common in the western pastoral area of the Mongolian ethnic group?",
    "options": [
      "Sky burial",
      "Cremation",
      "Sea burial",
      "Pagoda burial"
    ],
    "answer": "Sky burial"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the funeral customs of the Mongolian ethnic group before the founding of the People's Republic of China, after a person died, the body was placed on a ____ and dragged until it fell off.",
    "options": [
      "wooden cart",
      "sheepskin rug",
      "yurt",
      "grave"
    ],
    "answer": "wooden cart"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the sky burial of the Mongolian people before the founding of the People's Republic of China, bodies were placed in the wilderness and eaten by ____.",
    "options": [
      "wolves or wild eagles",
      "dogs or cats",
      "horses or sheep",
      "tigers or leopards"
    ],
    "answer": "wolves or wild eagles"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian ethnic group believes that after the corpse of the deceased is eaten in a sky burial, the soul of the deceased can ____.",
    "options": [
      "ascend to heaven",
      "enter hell",
      "remain in the human world",
      "be reincarnated"
    ],
    "answer": "ascend to heaven"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Mongolian culture before the founding of the People's Republic of China, during the sky burial, if the deceased's body was still present after seven days, it was considered inauspicious, and they had to continue inviting ____ to chant.",
    "options": [
      "Lama",
      "Wizard",
      "Shaman",
      "Taoist priest"
    ],
    "answer": "Lama"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the traditional Mongolian sky burial before the founding of New China, if the deceased's body remains after seven days, a lama must be invited to continue to ____.",
    "options": [
      "chant scriptures",
      "sing",
      "pray for rain",
      "dance"
    ],
    "answer": "chant scriptures"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Mongolian sky burial customs before the founding of the People's Republic of China, if the body is still present after seven days, offerings must be made to ____.",
    "options": [
      "Lama",
      "Monk",
      "Shaman",
      "Wizard"
    ],
    "answer": "Lama"
  },
  {
    "question": "Before the founding of the People's Republic of China, cremation among the Mongolian ethnic group was mainly for____.",
    "options": [
      "upper-level lamas",
      "nobility",
      "ordinary herdsmen",
      "farmers"
    ],
    "answer": "upper-level lamas"
  },
  {
    "question": "After the founding of the People's Republic of China, the Mongolian ethnic group completely switched to using ____ and cremation.",
    "options": [
      "water burial",
      "earth burial",
      "sky burial",
      "sea burial"
    ],
    "answer": "earth burial"
  },
  {
    "question": "The choice of burial practices of the Mongolian ethnic group mainly depends on the customs of ____.",
    "options": [
      "national laws",
      "religious beliefs",
      "family",
      "village"
    ],
    "answer": "family"
  },
  {
    "question": "In a Mongolian family, the one who holds the real power is ____.",
    "options": [
      "the eldest man in terms of seniority",
      "the married son",
      "the youngest son",
      "the eldest woman in terms of seniority"
    ],
    "answer": "the eldest man in terms of seniority"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the handling of major family matters among the Mongolian ethnic group, a man needs to obtain the approval of ____.",
    "options": [
      "the patriarch",
      "his brothers",
      "his wife",
      "his friends"
    ],
    "answer": "his wife"
  },
  {
    "question": "The sons of the Mongolian ethnic group ____ and then live separately, establishing their own households.",
    "options": [
      "born",
      "married",
      "come of age",
      "migrate"
    ],
    "answer": "married"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do Mongolian sons usually live after marriage?",
    "options": [
      "Near the parents' yurt",
      "In the village",
      "On the family homestead",
      "Near the city"
    ],
    "answer": "Near the parents' yurt"
  },
  {
    "question": "The inheritance method of the Mongolian ethnic group is ____.",
    "options": [
      "distributed annually",
      "one-time distribution",
      "installment distribution",
      "distributed at any time"
    ],
    "answer": "one-time distribution"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Mongolian culture, after the children get married, they ____ have the opportunity to distribute the family property again.",
    "options": [
      "still",
      "annually",
      "anytime",
      "do not"
    ],
    "answer": "do not"
  },
  {
    "question": "The children of the Mongolian ethnic group who live with their parents and are responsible for their parents' life in old age will be the ____ of all their parents' property.",
    "options": [
      "final heir",
      "initial heir",
      "sole caregiver",
      "temporary manager"
    ],
    "answer": "final heir"
  },
  {
    "question": "Many Mongolian herders love to play with ____.",
    "options": [
      "Dorang Yan Pipe",
      "Gaba",
      "Decorative Rope",
      "Decorative Smoking Pipe"
    ],
    "answer": "Decorative Smoking Pipe"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Mongolian culture, there is a saying 'exchange a smoking pipe for ____.'",
    "options": [
      "a sheep",
      "a cow",
      "a hat",
      "a horse"
    ],
    "answer": "a sheep"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mongolian tobacco pipes are usually fitted with ____ mouthpieces.",
    "options": [
      "red agate",
      "silver",
      "gold",
      "diamond"
    ],
    "answer": "red agate"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian tobacco pipe's stem is usually made of ____.",
    "options": [
      "sandalwood",
      "poplar",
      "felt",
      "silk"
    ],
    "answer": "sandalwood"
  },
  {
    "question": "The patterns on the smoking pipe of the Mongolian ethnic group usually include patterns such as ____.",
    "options": [
      "flowers, birds, fish, beasts",
      "silver dollars, buttons, beads and shells",
      "plants, animal horns",
      "orchards, flower beds"
    ],
    "answer": "flowers, birds, fish, beasts"
  },
  {
    "question": "Important festivals of the Mongolian ethnic group include Spring Festival, ____, and Naadam, among others.",
    "options": [
      "Rouzi Festival",
      "Gurbang Festival",
      "Xingchu Festival",
      "Nowruz Festival"
    ],
    "answer": "Xingchu Festival"
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the important festivals of the Mongolian ethnicity is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Nauryz",
      "Eid al-Adha",
      "Nowruz",
      "Naadam"
    ],
    "answer": "Naadam"
  },
  {
    "question": "The most grand and influential festival of the Mongolian people is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Nadam Fair",
      "Corban Festival",
      "Nowruz Festival",
      "Nawruz Festival"
    ],
    "answer": "Nadam Fair"
  },
  {
    "question": "The term 'Naadam' in Mongolian means ____ and is usually held in July or August each year.",
    "options": [
      "Entertainment or games",
      "Slaughtering livestock",
      "Breaking fast",
      "Memorial ceremony"
    ],
    "answer": "Entertainment or games"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian 'Naadam' is usually held in the ____ season.",
    "options": [
      "when the livestock are fat",
      "after the Gurban festival",
      "after Ramadan",
      "during the Nowruz festival"
    ],
    "answer": "when the livestock are fat"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nadam is an important festival of the Mongolian ethnic group, and its name in Mongolian means ____.",
    "options": [
      "Entertainment or games",
      "Fasting",
      "Animal slaughter",
      "Memorial"
    ],
    "answer": "Entertainment or games"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Nadam Festival of the Mongolian ethnic group is generally held in the month of ____ every year.",
    "options": [
      "7, 8",
      "9, 10",
      "3, 4",
      "5, 6"
    ],
    "answer": "7, 8"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Naadam Festival is held on the ____ , attracting Mongolian men and women, young and old to gather.",
    "options": [
      "Green Mountains",
      "Lush and beautiful grasslands",
      "Gobi Desert",
      "Lake"
    ],
    "answer": "Lush and beautiful grasslands"
  },
  {
    "question": "During the Naadam Festival, what is the common mode of transportation for Mongolian men, women, and children?",
    "options": [
      "Car",
      "Bicycle",
      "Horseback riding",
      "Walking"
    ],
    "answer": "Horseback riding"
  },
  {
    "question": "During the Naadam Festival, ______ is fluttering on the grassland.",
    "options": [
      "colorful flags",
      "red lanterns",
      "prayer flags",
      "blessing banners"
    ],
    "answer": "colorful flags"
  },
  {
    "question": "At the traditional Naadam Festival, only competitions of ____, horse racing, and wrestling are held.",
    "options": [
      "archery",
      "Mäshräp",
      "herding sheep",
      "dancing"
    ],
    "answer": "archery"
  },
  {
    "question": "At the Naadam Festival, one of the traditional competition events is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Horse racing",
      "Mêlée",
      "Running",
      "Mountain climbing"
    ],
    "answer": "Horse racing"
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the traditional competition events held by the Mongolian ethnic group at the Naadam Festival is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Wrestling",
      "Playing hockey",
      "Sheep butchering",
      "Dancing"
    ],
    "answer": "Wrestling"
  },
  {
    "question": "The traditional three skills of Mongolian men include wrestling, ____ and archery competitions.",
    "options": [
      "horse racing",
      "basketball",
      "soccer",
      "volleyball"
    ],
    "answer": "horse racing"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the modern Naadam, in addition to sports competitions, it also includes ____, cultural performances, picture exhibitions and film screenings.",
    "options": [
      "bonfire parties",
      "tea ceremony performances",
      "dragon boat races",
      "water-splashing festival"
    ],
    "answer": "bonfire parties"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mongolian wrestlers usually wear ____ on their feet.",
    "options": [
      "Mongolian boots",
      "slippers",
      "straw sandals",
      "sandals"
    ],
    "answer": "Mongolian boots"
  },
  {
    "question": "Some Mongolian wrestlers wear colorful ornaments around their necks called ____.",
    "options": [
      "Zanga",
      "Bu Shuai",
      "Mie Tie",
      "Bu Tiao"
    ],
    "answer": "Zanga"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian wrestler is bare-chested and wears ____. ",
    "options": [
      "wrestling pants",
      "robe",
      "white cloth",
      "white pants"
    ],
    "answer": "wrestling pants"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mongolian wrestlers wear an apron made of ____ around their waist.",
    "options": [
      "colorful silk",
      "fur",
      "cotton cloth",
      "white cloth"
    ],
    "answer": "colorful silk"
  },
  {
    "question": "The wrestling pants worn by Mongolian wrestlers are usually ____ in color.",
    "options": [
      "white",
      "red",
      "black",
      "blue"
    ],
    "answer": "white"
  },
  {
    "question": "When the music plays, Mongolian wrestlers enter the arena by dancing ____.",
    "options": [
      "Eagle Step",
      "Wolf Dance",
      "Dragon Dance",
      "Horse Dance"
    ],
    "answer": "Eagle Step"
  },
  {
    "question": "When Mongolian wrestlers enter the arena, they wave their arms as if ____ spreading their wings.",
    "options": [
      "eagle",
      "dragon",
      "galloping horse",
      "sacred wolf"
    ],
    "answer": "eagle"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Mongolian wrestling competitions, after the wrestlers perform the 'eagle dance', they immediately begin their ____.",
    "options": [
      "fight",
      "dance",
      "ritual",
      "singing"
    ],
    "answer": "fight"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian people have had a special affection for ____ since ancient times.",
    "options": [
      "Horse",
      "Cow",
      "Sheep",
      "Camel"
    ],
    "answer": "Horse"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian people have grown up on ____ since childhood.",
    "options": [
      "horseback",
      "camelback",
      "cowback",
      "sheepback"
    ],
    "answer": "horseback"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian people take pride in having a ____.",
    "options": [
      "fast horse",
      "fine cattle",
      "strong sheep",
      "camel horse"
    ],
    "answer": "fast horse"
  },
  {
    "question": "The unique skill of Mongolian herdsmen is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Training wild horses and being skilled at riding and shooting",
      "Lively metaphors and proverbs",
      "Patterns carved on scripture boards",
      "Worshiping nature for peace"
    ],
    "answer": "Training wild horses and being skilled at riding and shooting"
  },
  {
    "question": "The skills that Mongolian herders are good at include ____ and excellent riding and shooting.",
    "options": [
      "Training wild horses",
      "Ethnic dance",
      "Carving ritual objects",
      "Making mani stones"
    ],
    "answer": "Training wild horses"
  },
  {
    "question": "Expert horse riding and archery are one of the unique skills of ____.",
    "options": [
      "Mongolian herders",
      "Kazakh people",
      "Tibetan folk",
      "Dong villagers"
    ],
    "answer": "Mongolian herders"
  },
  {
    "question": "Another special skill of Mongolian herders is ____.",
    "options": [
      "training wild horses",
      "making fur products",
      "hunting musk and antlers",
      "carving rocks"
    ],
    "answer": "training wild horses"
  },
  {
    "question": "At the start of a Mongolian horse race, the riders are usually wearing ____.",
    "options": [
      "colorful belts",
      "white belts",
      "red belts",
      "green belts"
    ],
    "answer": "colorful belts"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the horse racing competition of the Mongolian ethnic group, riders tie ____ around their heads.",
    "options": [
      "colored scarf",
      "white band",
      "green cloth",
      "yellow scarf"
    ],
    "answer": "colored scarf"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Mongolian horse race, the riders line up in a ____ formation.",
    "options": [
      "straight line",
      "circle",
      "triangle",
      "rectangle"
    ],
    "answer": "straight line"
  },
  {
    "question": "As long as the Mongolian riders whistle from a distance, the horses will neigh and ____.",
    "options": [
      "gallop over",
      "turn around and run away",
      "stay still",
      "turn around and sleep"
    ],
    "answer": "gallop over"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian ethnic group is known as the '____ ethnic group'.",
    "options": [
      "Music",
      "Painting",
      "Dance",
      "Drama"
    ],
    "answer": "Music"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian ethnic group is known as the '____ ethnic group'.",
    "options": [
      "Drama",
      "Prose",
      "Poetry",
      "Calligraphy"
    ],
    "answer": "Poetry"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the folk songs passed down among the Mongolian ethnic group, there is a saying that describes the number of Mongolian folk songs in the Hetao region as '____'.",
    "options": [
      "Sung for three years, sang a cow's ear",
      "Sung for three years, haven't finished singing yet",
      "Sung for a year, sang a chicken feather",
      "Sung for a month, sang until out of breath"
    ],
    "answer": "Sung for three years, sang a cow's ear"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mongolian folk songs can be divided into ____ two genres.",
    "options": [
      "Prayers and wishes",
      "Fast-paced and soothing",
      "Muqam and instrumental",
      "Long-tune and short-tune"
    ],
    "answer": "Long-tune and short-tune"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mongolian folk songs fully reflect the ____ character of the Mongolian people.",
    "options": [
      "delicate and gentle",
      "simple, straightforward, enthusiastic, and bold",
      "calm and reserved",
      "passionate and sentimental"
    ],
    "answer": "simple, straightforward, enthusiastic, and bold"
  },
  {
    "question": "Listening to Mongolian folk songs gives people a feeling of ____.",
    "options": [
      "Being in the vast ocean",
      "Being in the bustling city",
      "Being in the Mongolian grassland",
      "Being in the deep mountains and old forests"
    ],
    "answer": "Being in the Mongolian grassland"
  },
  {
    "question": "\"Holboo\" is a widely popular form of folk singing among which ethnic group?",
    "options": [
      "Mongolian",
      "Uyghur",
      "Tibetan",
      "Miao"
    ],
    "answer": "Mongolian"
  },
  {
    "question": "\"Holboo\" has a fixed ____, and the lyrics are an impromptu creation inspired by the scene.",
    "options": [
      "melody",
      "instrument",
      "dance step",
      "costume"
    ],
    "answer": "melody"
  },
  {
    "question": "The lyrics of 'Holboo' are created by ____.",
    "options": [
      "improvisation",
      "prepared in advance",
      "traditional",
      "plagiarism"
    ],
    "answer": "improvisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "The praise words of the Mongolian ethnic group are called ____.",
    "options": [
      "Mahatala",
      "The Legend of Oguz Khan",
      "Ganjur",
      "Prayer Song"
    ],
    "answer": "Mahatala"
  },
  {
    "question": "The blessing words of the Mongolian ethnic group are called ____.",
    "options": [
      "Yu Re Le",
      "Horizontal Manuscript of Sanskrit Texts",
      "Aken Lyrics",
      "Oguz Kagan Narrative"
    ],
    "answer": "Yu Re Le"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian counterpart singing is called ____.",
    "options": [
      "Dairalcaa",
      "Uyghur Epic",
      "Tibetan Books",
      "Prayer Song"
    ],
    "answer": "Dairalcaa"
  },
  {
    "question": "The morin khuur is the most beloved ____ of the Mongolian people.",
    "options": [
      "national instrument",
      "traditional clothing",
      "language",
      "food"
    ],
    "answer": "national instrument"
  },
  {
    "question": "The morin khuur is named because the top of its neck is carved with a ____.",
    "options": [
      "horse head",
      "dragon head",
      "lion head",
      "eagle head"
    ],
    "answer": "horse head"
  },
  {
    "question": "The earliest horsehead fiddle was called ____.",
    "options": [
      "Xiqin",
      "Dutar",
      "Daf",
      "Yaks"
    ],
    "answer": "Xiqin"
  },
  {
    "question": "During the late Qing Dynasty, the morin khuur was called ____.",
    "options": [
      "Chao'er",
      "Rewap",
      "Yan Niu",
      "Dafu"
    ],
    "answer": "Chao'er"
  },
  {
    "question": "The morin khuur originated from the ____ of the Donghu.",
    "options": [
      "Xi",
      "Dutar",
      "Yak",
      "Daf"
    ],
    "answer": "Xi"
  },
  {
    "question": "The form of morin khuur performance in Mongolian culture is mostly ____.",
    "options": [
      "solo",
      "ensemble",
      "unison",
      "duet"
    ],
    "answer": "solo"
  },
  {
    "question": "The horsehead fiddle of the Mongolian ethnic group is sometimes played ____.",
    "options": [
      "by a choir",
      "self-accompanied singing",
      "formation performance",
      "accompanied by dance"
    ],
    "answer": "self-accompanied singing"
  },
  {
    "question": "The morin khuur is a traditional instrument of the ____ ethnic group.",
    "options": [
      "Tibetan",
      "Mongolian",
      "Han",
      "Kazakh"
    ],
    "answer": "Mongolian"
  },
  {
    "question": "The sound produced by the Mongolian horsehead fiddle is ____.",
    "options": [
      "dull and jarring",
      "vast and deep",
      "rapid and short",
      "high-pitched and intense"
    ],
    "answer": "vast and deep"
  },
  {
    "question": "The sound of the Morin khuur of the Mongolian ethnic group seems to take people into ____.",
    "options": [
      "plateau",
      "grassland",
      "forest",
      "desert"
    ],
    "answer": "grassland"
  },
  {
    "question": "The sound of the Mongolian horsehead fiddle gives a feeling of ____.",
    "options": [
      "melodious and pleasant",
      "short and rapid",
      "sharp and piercing",
      "dull and low"
    ],
    "answer": "melodious and pleasant"
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the traditional dances of the Mongolian ethnic group is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Shaman Dance",
      "Sabre Dance",
      "Tachiya Dance",
      "Cowhide Dance"
    ],
    "answer": "Sabre Dance"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Mongolian dance, there is a type of dance related to horseback riding called ____.",
    "options": [
      "Andai",
      "Rider",
      "Leather Dance",
      "Divination Dance"
    ],
    "answer": "Rider"
  },
  {
    "question": "____ is a traditional dance of the Mongolian ethnic group.",
    "options": [
      "Xiao Qing Ma",
      "Duet Dance",
      "Cloth Dance",
      "Cane Dance"
    ],
    "answer": "Xiao Qing Ma"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian horse dance moves are ____, with free and easy steps.",
    "options": [
      "clumsy and slow",
      "tall and bold",
      "cautious",
      "staggering"
    ],
    "answer": "tall and bold"
  },
  {
    "question": "The horse dance art of the Mongolian ethnic group was gradually refined from life on the prairie____.",
    "options": [
      "town",
      "on water",
      "mountain",
      "on horseback"
    ],
    "answer": "on horseback"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main religion believed by the Mongolian ethnic group is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Shamanism and Tibetan Buddhism",
      "Sunni and Ibadism",
      "Islam and Sunni",
      "Mahayana Buddhism and Tibetan Buddhism"
    ],
    "answer": "Shamanism and Tibetan Buddhism"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian ethnic group worships nature, such as ____.",
    "options": [
      "Sacrificial Oboo",
      "Magic Stone",
      "Bald Mountain",
      "Spells"
    ],
    "answer": "Sacrificial Oboo"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Mongolian ____ custom belongs to the category of Shamanism.",
    "options": [
      "Fire Sacrifice",
      "Calling the Clouds",
      "Offering Sacrifices",
      "Preaching"
    ],
    "answer": "Fire Sacrifice"
  },
  {
    "question": "The ____ culture of the Mongolian ethnic group is mainly influenced by Shamanism.",
    "options": [
      "Tree worship",
      "Prayer songs",
      "Exorcising evil spirits",
      "Gnawing on skulls"
    ],
    "answer": "Tree worship"
  },
  {
    "question": "Since the Ming dynasty, the religion that has been widely spread among the Mongolian people is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Islam",
      "Taoism",
      "Tibetan Buddhism",
      "Christianity"
    ],
    "answer": "Tibetan Buddhism"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the belief customs of the Mongolian ethnic group, there are still many elements of ____.",
    "options": [
      "Shamanism",
      "Taoism",
      "Islam",
      "Christianity"
    ],
    "answer": "Shamanism"
  },
  {
    "question": "The spread of Tibetan Buddhism among the Mongolian ethnic group had to absorb and integrate many forms and contents of ____.",
    "options": [
      "Islam",
      "Taoism",
      "Shamanism",
      "Christianity"
    ],
    "answer": "Shamanism"
  },
  {
    "question": "The main religion believed by the Mongolian ethnic group is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Tibetan Buddhism",
      "Sunni",
      "Polytheism",
      "Mahayana Buddhism"
    ],
    "answer": "Tibetan Buddhism"
  },
  {
    "question": "Since the 13th-century Yuan Dynasty, the Mongolian court converted to ____.",
    "options": [
      "Islam",
      "Buddhism",
      "Tibetan Buddhism",
      "Manichaeism"
    ],
    "answer": "Tibetan Buddhism"
  },
  {
    "question": "The religion widely practiced by the Mongolian herders is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Jingjiao",
      "Shamanism",
      "Zoroastrianism",
      "Christianity"
    ],
    "answer": "Shamanism"
  },
  {
    "question": "During the Yuan Dynasty, the religion that the Mongolian feudal ruling class converted to in their court was ____.",
    "options": [
      "Taoism",
      "Shamanism",
      "Tibetan Buddhism",
      "Christianity"
    ],
    "answer": "Tibetan Buddhism"
  },
  {
    "question": "During the Yuan Dynasty, the vast Mongolian herders still believed in ____.",
    "options": [
      "Islam",
      "Taoism",
      "Shamanism",
      "Buddhism"
    ],
    "answer": "Shamanism"
  },
  {
    "question": "From the latter half of the ____ century, many Mongolian aristocrats began to embrace the Gelug school of Tibetan Buddhism.",
    "options": [
      "16",
      "13",
      "15",
      "18"
    ],
    "answer": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Qing Dynasty, especially after Qianlong, the Mongolian tribal authorities adopted a comprehensive protection and reward policy towards ____.",
    "options": [
      "Mao Zedong Thought",
      "Taoism",
      "Islam",
      "Tibetan Buddhism"
    ],
    "answer": "Tibetan Buddhism"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Qing court not only encouraged various leagues and banners to build a large number of temples, but also had temples constructed by the personal decree of ____.",
    "options": [
      "Emperor",
      "National Master",
      "Dalai Lama",
      "Panchen Erdeni"
    ],
    "answer": "Emperor"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Qing Dynasty, the upper class of Mongolian monks formed a large ____ group coexisting with secular feudal lords.",
    "options": [
      "sorcerers",
      "peasants",
      "clerical feudal lords",
      "guests"
    ],
    "answer": "clerical feudal lords"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the daily life of the Mongolian people, activities such as moving camps, marriage, birth, aging, sickness, and death are all prognosticated for fortune and misfortune, and transcendence by ____.",
    "options": [
      "Swordsman",
      "Lama",
      "Doctor",
      "Shaman"
    ],
    "answer": "Lama"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mongolian teenagers were often encouraged by feudal dynasties to leave home and become ____.",
    "options": [
      "Lamas",
      "Auls",
      "Serfs",
      "Herdsmen"
    ],
    "answer": "Lamas"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Mongolian culture, a lama does not ____.",
    "options": [
      "marry",
      "herd",
      "move",
      "farm"
    ],
    "answer": "marry"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Mongolian culture, lamas do not participate in ____.",
    "options": [
      "social production",
      "family ceremonies",
      "religious activities",
      "tribal meetings"
    ],
    "answer": "social production"
  },
  {
    "question": "With the spread of ____, scholars among the lamas played a role in the cultural exchange between Mongolia and Tibet.",
    "options": [
      "Han Chinese Buddhism",
      "Taoism",
      "Tibetan Buddhism",
      "Islam"
    ],
    "answer": "Tibetan Buddhism"
  },
  {
    "question": "The construction of Lama temples in Mongolian areas took place during the Ming and Qing dynasties, such as the ____ in Darhan Muminggan United Banner.",
    "options": [
      "Bailing Temple",
      "Potala Palace",
      "Jokhang Temple",
      "Reliquary Temple"
    ],
    "answer": "Bailing Temple"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Mongolian region, Xin Barag Left Banner has the famous ____ Temple.",
    "options": [
      "Ganzhur",
      "Hongshanding",
      "Tubaby",
      "Cha Temple"
    ],
    "answer": "Ganzhur"
  },
  {
    "question": "The famous temple in Guyang County, Mongolian area is ____. ",
    "options": [
      "Wudangzhao",
      "Sera Monastery",
      "Space Temple",
      "Manba Monastery"
    ],
    "answer": "Wudangzhao"
  },
  {
    "question": "The famous temple in Xilin Gol of the Mongolian ethnic group is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Beizi Temple",
      "Guge Temple",
      "Sunshine Temple",
      "Cuoji Temple"
    ],
    "answer": "Beizi Temple"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Meidai Zha of Tumote Right Banner is a Mongolian ____.",
    "options": [
      "temple",
      "Tibetan racetrack",
      "guesthouse",
      "snow lotus valley"
    ],
    "answer": "temple"
  },
  {
    "question": "The religions that the Mongolian ethnic group has historically believed in include Shamanism and ____.",
    "options": [
      "Nestorianism",
      "Buddhism",
      "Tibetan Buddhism",
      "Sunni Islam"
    ],
    "answer": "Tibetan Buddhism"
  },
  {
    "question": "Apart from Tibetan Buddhism, the Mongolian people historically also believed in ____.",
    "options": [
      "Islam",
      "Catholicism",
      "Manichaeism",
      "Nestorianism"
    ],
    "answer": "Islam"
  },
  {
    "question": "Among the Mongolian ethnic group, there is still a small population that believes in ____.",
    "options": [
      "Christianity",
      "Hinduism",
      "Chinese Buddhism",
      "Taoism"
    ],
    "answer": "Christianity"
  },
  {
    "question": "A small number of people in the Mongolian ethnic group believe in ____ and Islam.",
    "options": [
      "Taoism",
      "Christianity",
      "Shamanism",
      "Buddhism"
    ],
    "answer": "Christianity"
  },
  {
    "question": "The two religions that are still believed by a minority among the Mongolian ethnic group are Christianity and ____.",
    "options": [
      "Hinduism",
      "Shamanism",
      "Islam",
      "Primitive Religion"
    ],
    "answer": "Islam"
  }
]